question_data = [
    {
        "question": "The border between Mexico and the United States is the busiest in the world, and is one of the largest. "
                    "According to the International Commission of Borders and Water (CILA) it spans 3,185 kilometers.",
        "answer": "True",
    },
    {
        "question": "The first INFONAVIT in Mexico was built in Cancun. This institute is responsible for granting "
                    "credits to those workers who wish to purchase a new home.",
        "answer": "False",
    },
    {
        "question": "Zona Río is the 4th most important financial district in Mexico.",
        "answer": "True",
    },
    {
        "question": "Tijuana has one of the most beautiful scenic roads in Mexico.",
        "answer": "True",
    },
    {
        "question": "Tijuana has the only seaside bullring in the whole world. With a capacity of 40 thousand people, "
                    "it’s the second largest bullring in the country after Plaza México.",
        "answer": "False",
    },
    {
        "question": "TThe Tijuana motto, “Aquí comienza la patria” (“The homeland starts here”), was the starting "
                    "phrase in the speech of presidential candidate Adolfo López Mateos "
                    "during his visit to Tijuana in 1958.",
        "answer": "True",
    },
    {
        "question": "The Cosmopolitan Tower is the smart building that complies with the highest sustainability "
                    "certifications in all of the northwest. With this tower, Tijuana already has three "
                    "sustainable buildings.",
        "answer": "True",
    },
    {
        "question": "The 11 of July, 1900 is considered the official date of the founding of the City of Tijuana.",
        "answer": "False",
    },
    {
        "question": "Tijuana produces 80% of the world’s digital thermometers.",
        "answer": "False",
    },
    {

        "question": "With the new border-crossing bridge of the Tijuana International Airport into San Diego the city "
                    "will become more attractive to investors and tourists.",
        "answer": "True",
    },
    {
        "question": "Tijuana is one of the main television assembly cities in the world, thanks to the great "
                    "concentration of assembly plants.",
        "answer": "True",
    }
]
